♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
You guys know what this meeting's about?
- No idea.
- How about you, Morning Breath Mike?
I have no idea.
Listen up, everyone.
Sales are down across the board,
but mostly we're failing to connect
with a group called "millennials."
I saw this guy cry one time.
To learn more
about our target demographic,
we're all gonna watch
this instructional video.
News on the March
Millennials. Who are they?
What do the want?
A millennial can be defined
as anyone born between 1982 and 2000.
Or anyone who thinks loving
sriracha or Austin, Texas,
counts as a personality.
Millennials crave things like:
instant gratification,
authentic experiences,
and, for some reason
we haven't figured out yet,
improv comedy.
Here's one millennial who has a parakeet
with nine million followers on Snapchat.
Here's another
who singlehandedly started
the hashtags that cancelled
12 network TV shows
she found offensive.
And now I'm told
she identifies as a man,
so I'm being fired.
Hello. I'm your new announcer.
And actually, he was just about done.
Thank you and good day.
So please welcome someone who's
gonna help us reach millennials,
our new head of social media, Hammer.
Oh. He just group-texted us "hello."
And now here comes a text
from the guy who doesn't know
this is a group text.
"Nice to meet you, Hammer.
Let's have lunch later,
and I'll tell you who's gay."
Right on. 'Sup? I'm Hammer.
Uh, first I'd like
to not thank you for hiring me,
because I just expect
good things to happen to me
without working for them.
Second, I'd like to give you all
a list of my trigger warnings.
What's a trigger warning?
Actually, brah, asking me
what a trigger warning is
is one of my triggers, brah.
I feel traumatized, brah.
And now I'm tweeting about you, brah.
And now you're trending, brah.
And now your life is ruined, brah.
And now you're fired, brah.
What... what happened to Brah?
Also, the lack of diversity here
is horrifying, brah.
Uh, Brah is gone.
Now, if we want to get
some social media attention,
we got to start with a group selfie.
Um, excuse me. Didn't Ellen
do this, like, three years ago?
Hey, does Taye Diggs
follow you on Twitter?
No, but Kraft Singles does.
That's what I thought.
And... posted.
Do you know what I just did?
I just made you all viral.
Also, my band is playing tonight
at an inconvenient time.
It's six un-showered guys
and a pale woman with a ukulele
shouting "Hey!" in unison.
Because that's what music is now.
♪ Hey! ♪
What is this?
They just keep saying "hey."
I know. It's my favorite song.
Oh, 'cause "hay" is for horses.
Hey, guys.
You want to have a smoke break?
What? We can't smoke inside.
It's not smoking, Peter. It's vaping.
Everyone's doing it... Even Darth Vaper.
I find your lack of vape disturbing.
Come on, Peter, give it a shot.
What happened? All of a sudden
I feel like I know better
than everyone else!
That's because anytime
someone walks through a cloud
of vape smoke, a millennial is born.
I think I feel it!
Broad City is so funny.
No, Broad City is genius.
No, no. Broad City is everything!
There it is. Grossly exaggerating
the quality of a just-okay TV show.
Peter, you're officially a millennial.
Hey, you want a ride
in the Millennial Falcon?
Ah, look at that...
We found another one!
Peter, a rite of passage
for any millennial
is attending Coachella.
It's a great place to see bands
that are either really new
or really old.
- Which one should we see?
- Well, on the main stage,
it's Tame Impala that formed
in an UberPOOL on the way here.
And on the side stage,
it's "Neil Young asleep"
in front of the television."
I always get him confused with
Bloom County's Bill the Cat.
Peter, you're doing great
as a millennial.
Next thing is you got to learn
how to be on Fleek.
"On fleek"? People still say "on fleek"?
No, Peter, that's not what I meant.
I want you on Fleek.
This is Fleek.
Oh, can I ride him?!
Sure, Peter. Get on Fleek.
♪ ♪
Yay!
Our country's involved
in six different wars,
but millennials think about this stuff.
Remember, Peter, never walk anywhere
when you can ride
something weird instead.
What's that?
Sorry, I was taking a selfie
while shooting a Snapchat
while Periscoping that Snapchat
while Instagramming latte art
while Shazaming The Weekend
while streaming Master of None
while retweeting George Takei
while saying, "This wins the Internet!"
while still being ♪soooo bored.
Hammer?
Hammer? Come on, man, don't
make me look up from my phone.
Oh, you're texting me.
Oh, no! Hammer!
You! Call 911!
You! Give me your shirt
to make a tourniquet!
You! Snap a pic.
Clarendon filter. Clarendon!
Hammer, stay with me, buddy.
Peter, if I die,
chop my body up
and serve me as street tacos.
So selfless.
No! I won't let you be made into tacos!
Peter... it's-it's too late.
Listen, I've got this idea
for a business, and...
I want you to have it.
It's artisanal.
A-Artisanal...
Artisanal what? Is it pretzels?
Is it artisanal pretzels?!
Has that been done?
Does anyone know if
artisanal pretzels is a thing?
It seems so obvious, yet I
don't think I've ever seen them.
I better do millennial CPR.
One... ugh, whatever...
Two... ugh, whatever...
Three... ugh, I'm gonna let
my parents take care of this.
I've never been to a millennial funeral.
Yeah, it seems in poor taste
that they hired Keyboard Cat.
Assembled congregants,
no worries to you.
And also to you.
Let us tweet.
Peter, why is he naked in there?
It's an environmental statement.
Lois, please stop looking
at my dead friend's dong.
Listen, I made breakfast and drove,
so if there's a dead dong,
I'm gonna look at it!
We've all lost
a great friend-slash-barista-
slash-deejay-
slash-Genius Bar employee-
slash-person with a yellow highlighter
at the Best Buy exit.
And now a reading
from the book of JustJared.
"Death be the ultimate fail."
Peter, I hate to do this here,
but you were good friends with Hammer,
and business at the brewery must go on.
That's why, as of today,
I'm making you head of social media.
Hey, whatever you want.
I'm a team player.
I was even one of the 300.
Hey, does 299 work?
'Cause I got to go diarrhea
off the cliff.
We now return to Marvel's The Offenders.
Good morning, you see.
I gathered you all together...
Kevin Spacey,
Roman Polanski...
Hey, hey, hey...
Woody Allen, Steven Seagal,
Matt Lauer with the Pudding Pop,
Brett Ratner,
and you, lesser-known offender
James Toback.
Don't forget me!
Harvey shower!
I-I... I-Is Matt Damon coming?
No, but he knows about all of us.
He's very aware of what's
going on here, you see.
All right, guys, I got to come
up with some social media ideas
for the brewery. What do ya got?
Oh, you want viral?
You asked the right guy.
You remember Leeroy Jenkins?
- Yeah.
- Right.
- What do you mean, "right"?
- You know, Leeroy Jenkins.
- What about him?
- Do that.
Joe, you can't... That already happened.
Do it again. This time with beer.
Hang on a sec.
- Thank you.
- How about some fruit in the beer?
No, guys, we need
social media-specific plans
to reach a younger audience.
You remember "Charlie Bit My Finger"?
Do that.
You know what? I give up.
We've given this...
what, almost a minute?
Peter, that's the problem
with kids today...
They have no attention span.
Wait. That's it!
We'll do a show for people
with no attention span.
We'll call it The Six Second Talk Show.
Well, I guess that could work.
But it's just so sad
that young people can't pay attention
to something longer than six sec...
Oh, oh, my God.
JOE and PETER and CLEVELAND: Whoa!
What the hell, you guys? I was talking.
You know, there's more to life
than just what's on your phone.
Wrong, idiot.
Anyone know how
to turn these things off?
All right, Six Second Talk Show
in three, two...
I'm Peter Griffin, and this is
the Six Second Talk Show.
My guest tonight is Joe Biden.
And that's all the time we have.
Thanks for watching. Good night.
- How was that?
- Eh, it kind of dragged.
Well, Congress is at it again.
Good night.
It's The Six Second Talk Show,
and now, your host, here...
Welcome to The Six Second Talk Show.
I'm Peter Griffin, and now our
musical guest, Barenaked Ladies.
- ♪ It's been... ♪
- I'd like to thank our musical guest,
Barenaked Ladies. Good night.
Peter, I can't believe your talk show
is such a huge hit for the brewery.
And thanks to that, I'm now
a huge social media star.
Oh, my God, what the hell is that?
Hello, Griffin family.
I'm coming to you live,
via living room hologram.
I'm Parker Stanton, CEO of Boop,
the most powerful company
in Silicon Valley.
- Do you know Mr. Skin?
- Ah!
- We'll talk later.
Look, Peter, the reason I'm here
is because of your Six Second Talk Show.
Now, I haven't had the time to watch it,
but I hear it's the buzz
of Silicon Valley.
I want you and your family
to visit us here as my guests,
so I can find out
what the next big thing is.
Oh, I-I got lots of ideas.
I've been working on something
called "Look At It, Kick It."
Look at it...
Excuse me, can I help you?
Kick it!
Pure genius.
See you in Silicon Valley.
Oh, this is exciting.
A family trip.
Yeah, I love traveling.
Oh, except that trip to Europe
where we spent most of our time
trying to refold our map.
All right, the museum is that way,
so let's fold the map and go.
Okay, couple more folds...
Nope, okay, wrong end.
Now, let's see...
Nope, nope, that's wrong...
Find the corners.
It's not a puzzle, Chris.
Y-You got to fold on the creases.
I'd be able to find the creases
if somebody had folded it
correctly last time.
I did fold it correctly.
Nope, you didn't, and then,
you jammed it into a backpack
and now I'm in this mess.
Don't blame me, you ripped it up
when you were tearing through
the backpack for your snacks.
Okay, this is why I wanted
to bring a globe, all right?
You don't have to fold a globe.
Who the hell would bring
a globe on vacation?
See, Bon? We're eating food,
and they're tearing each other apart.
Where to next, mon ch├йri?
Welcome to Boop.
As our name suggests,
our mainframe connects to
and powers virtually
every server on the globe.
Without Boop, there is no Internet.
Hey, Parker. Are we still on
for the Samsung Galaxy Note
meeting after lunch?
Yep. Are-are the test results in?
Yeah, but...
Let's save it for the meeting.
Where's your nearest bathroom?
Gender-fluid?
Yes, there will be a lot of that.
Hmm, must be one of them
high-tech Japanese toilets.
♪ I'm gonna pee into electrical urinal ♪
♪ And make the sparks go higher. ♪
I'm having so much fun.
What the hell is going on?
Our mainframe is having a meltdown!
Hang on, let me flush.
You idiot.
You shut down the entire Internet.
How could you do that?
This is the most irresponsible
thing that I've ever...
Although I was incensed by this man,
I had to admire his courage
for leaving his penis out
the entire time I was yelling at him.
As a man who struggles
with body dysmorphia,
I couldn't help but be impressed
by that kind of self-confidence.
As I stood there,
being berated by this man,
I couldn't help but notice
his searching gaze.
Years later,
we would bump into each other
at a small cafe in Rome and
reminisce about this moment.
And later still, recreate it
in a small bed and breakfast
at the bottom of the Spanish Steps.
But that's a story for another time.
Or, as they say in Italian, molto homo.
Peter, you've done some stupid things,
but crashing the Internet has
to be the dumbest yet.
Look at the chaos you've caused.
I have no idea
how to drive without texting.
Why can't I post this video?
- Hello.
- What did you say?
Why aren't you looking
at your phone, you psycho?
Why is no one liking my posts?
Well, I hate all your posts!
Hello.
Peter, Lois is right.
This mess is all your fault.
Settle down, Brian.
I'm sure life will be just fine
without the Internet.
Maybe we can even go see
that Amish comedian.
Sir, where are you from?
Chicago.
I have never been to Chicago.
How about you, sir?
Boston!
I have never been to Boston.
Anyone here from the back fields
of Pennsylvania, Ohio
or upstate New York?
No!
Then I have been Jebediah, son of Abner.
How are we gonna get back
to the airport?
There's no Internet,
which means there's no GPS,
which means we can't use Uber.
Okay, I have a crazy idea.
Let's get a cab.
There's a taxi stand.
Dead.
Dead...
Barely alive.
To the airport.
Now, because you can't stare
at your phone anymore,
enjoy a disturbingly loud clip
of Jimmy Fallon on cab TV.
Tonight, get ready to lose
all respect for Al Pacino
when I force him to play a game
meant for children!
This.
This is why Uber.
No Netflix, no Hulu, no Amazon...
I'm so bored.
Come on, Meg, you're overreacting.
We still got network TV.
We now return to Kevin Can Wait on CBS.
Well, that's not gonna work.
Okay, everybody, don't panic.
We'll just do what people did
before the Internet.
We can play charades.
Oh, you mean like your marriage?
Chris, I told you that in confidence.
Dad, you got to do something.
Nobody can live without the Internet.
Ah, you're right. This sucks.
It's even worse
than when I was roommates
with Oscar Pistorius.
Somebody's in here.
Somebody's in here!
I'm the one who screwed this up.
I'll be the one to fix it.
I'll be the Internet.
What are you talking about?
We can do all the things
we loved about the Internet.
We just got to do it without technology.
From now on,
if you want to tweet something,
you do it the old-fashioned way:
write it on a piece of paper,
staple it to a bird,
and throw it out the door.
Hey, do you follow Peter Griffin
on Twitter?
No. Why? Is he funny?
No, he just throws dead birds
on his lawn.
It's awesome.
Great news, Chris. I figured out
how to recreate the best part of
the Internet.
I've got pictures of five celebrities
who you'd never believe used to be fat.
- Great, let's see 'em.
- Sure, buddy.
But first you have to watch
this unwelcome pop-up ad.
I don't want probiotics.
Then press the "skip ad" button.
Why should I do all this work?
They're really good pictures, Chris.
Number three will shock you.
Okay, I'll press it.
Oh, no! You pressed in the wrong place,
and now you're being sent
to the ad's website,
which also has additional pop-ups.
This is a nightmare!
Just tell me one of 'em.
Kenan Thompson.
That's not a surprise!
Peter? What are you doing?
Oh, I'm your Waze app today.
- You on your way to work?
- Yeah, I am.
All right, you will be there
in six minutes.
Just start heading straight.
Okay, sounds good.
- So, how's everything at...
- Take a right! Right now!
Geez, okay, calm down.
Left! Take a left immediately!
Would you like to upgrade
to an ad-free experience for $4.99?
- No.
- Try new Domino's Pizza.
Hey, Peter, who are these guys?
Oh, this is just my looping GIF
of black teens reacting
to a very mild burn.
Huh. Sounds kind of pointless.
Oh, you mean like your feet?
All right, trying to be
the Internet is impossible.
I wish I never peed on that server.
You know, when my phone gets wet,
I just put it in a bag of rice.
Shut up, Meg. That's dumb.
I've done that before. It works.
Chris, that's brilliant.
We just need a big bag
and a lot of rice.
You sure that's gonna work?
Eh, worth a shot.
We'll just have to roll up our sleeves
and do the best we can,
like the men who built New York City.
Men, creating an entire
subway system out of nothing
is grueling, thankless,
life-threatening work.
But just remember: we're doing this
so that one day,
future commuters can be hassled
by panhandlers
and amateur break-dancers.
What about public masturbators?
Especially public masturbators.
Now, let's go die underground!
Look, we're getting a signal.
I think we fixed the Internet.
Something's coming through.
It looks like an ad.
"Smithwick's Artisinal Pretzels."
Son of a bitch!
Well, I'm glad you got the Internet...
H-Hold on.
I'm sorry, what-what were you saying?
Yeah, sounds good.
And send.
Take that, Delta Air Lines.
Submitted for your approval:
a restaurant full of people
so distracted by their phones,
they're unaware that they're all
about to go up in smoke,
just like the Fox Tuesday night lineup.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru